Hello, I saw 1 person.
Um, it
's a bit dark.
Ah, Apple's Honey. Nice to meet you. Ah, j. Hello, I
'll turn the light a little brighter.
Just a moment. 0.
Ugh.
4.
Works. 4. My
hair is really long, but I need to cut it.
Do you know? Internet. Dia. It's falling.
Then, what does
this light source do?
5.
Ha Tae-hoon. This house's dog is here.
5. It'll be okay.
Light. 8. 4. Mimi. Side. Hello.
Show me your height. Keep looking. Study. 1. Ah, exactly.
But now, depending on the lighting, you know.
Yes, no. Now, and
the camera
is too. This year's blooming. The group uploaded the language video.
When I was filming, I was a bit nervous, so I didn't know well.
After filming, while editing the video, I saw that
I was now forming a pharos. I was looking at the ground, and my body was
lowered like this.
In the noun, the camera was high, but my monitor was low,
so that's why. It's a
shame. Baek Mo.
Amen. I need to take a better picture. Mint chocolate. Sedimentation. Leica. Ran. 520. Nice to meet you. It
's your first time. Ah, it seems.
In today's video, it's a book.  There may be many who haven't seen it since it was
recently released, but this is one of the reasons why you should drink raw milk that isn't made for you. In fact, there are so many of them, so I'm writing about them again even though it's been a while.
I wrote about this a while ago, and I'm going to
squeeze it out. Why is it called a false accusation? At that time, when sterilization was done, the kitchen was rich in support. It was destroyed and deactivated. I used expressions like that, but I
only wrote about one line. I wanted to talk about it in more detail. In the
case of Ruta Chiun, I covered how the protein in the stomach is contained, how it is newly added, and
how much it is destroyed when it is established.
Hello, Enjoyed. Hello, Shopping. No. Yes.
So, if you have any further questions, please ask. There are
so many of them. You should drink a lot of milk. Then,
after the actual liver, I'd like to look into stories related to the throat and other things in more detail.
Among them, lactoferrin and atopy also come out, and I'm going to talk about how these things play a role. How can
milk that hasn't been confirmed be healthier or safer than milk that hasn't been confirmed? How can
I prevent other bacteria?
I want to talk about how safe it is and how good it is, and I've
written down a fair amount in writing, so I haven't gone into detail yet.
Oh my god, hello. If you freeze the system, it
doesn't
metabolize protein. That protein is fragile. It's
especially true for fermented eggs and minji. When dogs are crushed or
exposed to excessive heat, the
shape becomes distorted and deteriorates.
In general,
especially when it's cold, there is
n't much protein in the cheese.
Moreover, cheese is
made by adding rennet or something like that, and the
hard proteins that remain are
extracted rather than hard proteins. We make cheese by collecting only the curds and excluding the casein.
Since the casein is removed during the cheese-making process, it has
much more casein and is stable as a medium.
Regarding the oxidation problem of those proteins, let's talk about
sparring.  I saw that
the meeting was expensive, but what would be better if it was human? It would be
nice to look healthy and loving, right?
That's actually the 3rd stage. Homemade formula is
practically impossible for some mothers for some reason. They may be unhealthy, or they
may have had a sudden accident or language disorder, or there are many other reasons. In such cases,
there are contents that talk about how breastfeeding is a healthy choice or a healthy method.
How can I use my power hair in a
situation where I can't feed my child?
There are things like milk banks. I see other people. How do many
mothers come out? In the aftermath, there are so many dogs now that I'm worried. I do
n't know if you can hear the barking.
Hello, Young. Anyway, now,
rather than gathering at a bank and receiving donations or using things that were donated, I recommend making your own homemade formula.
And A4 Miller is
not ground milk, but for some reason, it's
made similar to human breast milk, and various nutrients are added to it.
Cow's milk, gather around. The
nutritional content isn't exactly the same. There are many things like that. Now, there are rough ones, and you can
dilute it by mixing it with water. Yes,
now, I'd rather make it yourself than do that.
That mother, who donated to the Oyu Bank, but who
squeezed out the reserves for her children to eat,
really knows exactly how much she ate. I'd
rather make it myself than do that. That's exactly what I'm talking about.
In the end, just as the
nutrients in milk vary depending on what the cow ate, the same goes for people.
How did they live? Did they get a lot of T-nut pitch? Just like how many ribs you see, it's
good to see a lot of people. It's
good for me. I
'm a beginner at LS, but if you look at it the same way,
or if you lose weight, there are many stories. I'm in the middle of it a lot, so the public and private sectors are
excluded. Sports punishment. The
lab is three-fold.
The word "S" curve. The seller reacts more, so I wonder if it's unfair to the heart.
Eat white rice or half a small bowl of rice together.
First,
did you get tested to see if your heart is not in good condition before, or just
skip it if you see hematuria with a urine step test.  I think we need to consider whether you've tried anything else.
Oh,
yes, but generally, eating a lot of meat or something like that doesn't put a strain on the kidneys and cause further damage. The kidneys aren't
already completely destroyed.
In fact, a high-protein diet is better for the kidneys.
Eating a lot of it is the same.
When you're underweight, there's
not much difference in dieting. This doesn't mean everyone loses weight, and I lose weight
very quickly. I
think losing weight and returning to a normal weight is ultimately the same.
People who want to gain weight and those who want to lose weight will have different approaches, but it's
important to eat a lot and eat more often, exercise a lot, and do something else.
I mean, people need to get enough sleep, and those things are
generally the same. My
job is to eat kefir thickened for about 36 hours, but if you catch it, it's like an inflammatory reaction. If you
eat it fermented, it might be better.
I think it's better to not eat protein at
all when an immune disease or inflammatory reaction appears. Yes, you can try guidance after you've recovered, but when you're already reacting, even a very
small amount reacts. It even reacts to ghee.  Even if there are people,
it's really just a little bit. To put it simply, some
people react even when cooking in the same space.
I mentioned this in a KakaoTalk chatroom, not on Life iZone Live, but in the past.
There are cases where people with autoimmune diseases have been treated by Khan, who has special needs.
When families cook together in the same space, no matter how much they change their diet,
there are some areas that don't improve. They say it's gotten a lot better, but
even if you use and wash the same utensils, no matter how much you
wash, a reaction can occur simply by using the same cooking utensils and using the same utensils. Even if you
eat just enough to not cause a reaction, it can still happen. In that case,
stop for now. After at least a certain amount of time has passed, and you've determined that the autoimmune reaction and
inflammatory response are
no longer real, it would be a good idea to try it.
How do you hunt for colostrum powder and
take it out? You shouldn't eat clothes made with powder.
Of course, if you eat colostrum powder, the colostrum protein inside is good for the industry,
but if it's
freeze-dried, at least enzymes and
various
things like the immune system, like Lee Min-ho's global ring, are
very helpful.  But on the other hand, there are definitely some negative aspects to this.
So, I don't think there's anything dumb about the price, even if you have to suppress the Korean language.
rhk sur is better. Please settle down and use it.
Well-being. How can you fill it with overheating? The military has
lungs. What is it? The head of the nearby village is in a state of personal contact with the man's clothes.
Yes, there are more dairy farms around than you might think. Even if you
go further in the metropolitan area, it's
a bit difficult to find in the center of Seoul, but of course, if you go out a little bit, you can find
quite a lot in places like Gimpo and other places. If you deal directly with them,
of course, it's factory-style. Oh, here, but you
can put it in.
Originally, what's good about my mother's experience growing up at home?
I have a plan. When we gather for the second child, how about squeezing it a little more and having the third child? Oh, that's also good.
If the first mother ate well, there's nothing better than that.
But that can happen.
Human breast milk has the most linoleic acid in the world. It
can be seen as one of the biggest differences from cow's milk. As you know,
Seoul Milk has butter, as you can see if you cut it with a cutter.
Linoleic acid is very low and
both polyunsaturated fatty acids are quite high. But human breast milk is higher than you think.
That's why babies get plump and fat after eating it. It
contains sugar and a
lot of sugar. There's a lot of sugar and
a lot of fat. The fat is high in linoleic acid, so the upper part of the stomach is loosened.
Um,
yes, so
it's good for the firstborn, but it might not be necessarily good.
In that sense, the reason
we drink cow's milk is not because we are sinful. It's
just because cow's milk is good for the young body. The nutrients are helpful to us, it's
bioavailable, and it's easy to digest. We drink it because of that. It
's not because we can't drink milk, so that
's part of it. Of course, it's good.
Oh, and if it's easy and your
arms don't gain weight, it's good for the firstborn to be thin.
When I made it today, when I made Tom Pomelo, I put 15 servings of tripe in
4 or 5 servings. Oh, I had
joint pain that I couldn't do, so
milk helps the joints. It's really good for the firstborn.
From the beginning, this is a factor.
Hello, Class Ena Meng. I
didn't have the previous 2nd generation force, and I
only guessed that it would be AJ in-depth at the hospital. My kidney function is normal, but it's a
problem every year. My immune system is rotting and destroying the channel. You
have an autoimmune kidney disease.
Fortunately, my creatinine level is within the normal range. The hospital found out about the low protein period, so I let it
go in one ear and out the other. I had a $2 test for functional adversity and
found out that I was allergic to too many foods. I received the genre, that is, the morning. The
stock price is a small amount, so I'm polite.
When you do 5 flashes,
if you say it's a period of reflux, Jake Abelson Press Altar is a diet that
basically
refers to a reflux diet, so the spectrum is very wide.
For example, even if you use a thumb, eating as much bread as you want can fall into the category of a strategy.
Of course, now I
recommend that you don't use wireless products as your main source of nutrition, but you
can still eat a lot of bread, and you can
also eat vegetables.
4 years old and older, many people can't eat too many things, but they pull it well and use
various
reflux clocks and 0 0
seasonings.  Eating seasoned foods or chromium
can be considered a crime, and eating various fruits can also be considered a crime. It's
a bit like that, but you
can eat various grains after handling them well, and even after they've passed, you can eat them after pre-processing them.
However, if you have an underlying condition such as an autoimmune disease or a
KakaoTalk mind, it
's better to take the bookstore much more tightly.
Especially in the case of autoimmune diseases, it's not clear exactly which food or plant toxin you
're reacting to.
Or, it's not just plant toxins, but environmental issues can also come up.
In particular, not being able to sleep well at night every year can be a problem. Is
n't it a genre that promotes drinking in a glass?
Yes, now when those parts are unclear, it's especially good to
know only what we need, and it's better to cultivate things that taste similar to unnecessary things.
Then, rather than a comprehensive eating habit called just pickling, it would be
better to stick to a protective diet close to the caliber or Lee Je-young. Eat
just the amount of protein you need at the time and
make sure to eat enough fat.  I
think that would be better.
4 If you have an autoimmune disease and are not sure if you react to U protein dairy products, you should
not eat this product either.
This product is
truly a much better food, and
if we eat high-quality products, it contains all the nutrients we need to live, and
not only nutrients, but also some elements and other substances. It is a
truly perfect food, but
it is not that people cannot live without it. There are many things that need to be taken care of.
For example, if you just drink milk and eat cheese, you
have to eat a star once in a while. It
is not easy to just chew and eat you, so eat you in between.
There are also people who have poor digestion, but it is not something that you can just not eat because you don't like it.
Or, you can boil the bones until they are crumbled like this. Or, you can
add vinegar and drink it.
But vinegar can also be bad for you. In extreme cases, you can
boil it for a long time and
eat you a little bit. For example, if you make it into an example of calcium,
then you can
drink it and solve the problem by
not drinking milk and other things.  In order to match the foods, you need to be
more careful when planning your diet. In that sense, this
product is really good, but
there are people who react to dairy products, especially protein. I think the root cause is probably
excessive consumption of rebar products in the past, or continuous consumption of sterilized products when there are many elders.
Regardless of the root cause, if I'm not feeling well right now and am reacting to the comeback question, no matter how good the food is, it's better to eat 1 unit and
multiply it by 5. Moreover, you
don't necessarily have to eat 4 units of
butter. Next, this is a really, really good food that contains all of the D-types of Kate,
and it also
contains 3 fatty acids. Of course,
Evita Mail Kate loses, so please putter 1 direction. I can get it, and
radar can always eat Kate, and I
can fill up sufficiently by eating other fatty acids. I'm a
good sleeper, but if I do 100,000 Jordan, I can't get a deep sleep. I'm not
sure if I should fast or if my body isn't ready yet.  I'm curious. Some
people make mistakes like when they eat only Sika and it doesn't go away at night because the sound goes up. In
that case, I
don't think you need to do it if you can't sleep at the time of Castle. There's no need to force it.
There may be times when you have no choice but to fast, but if that's not the case, it's not like you
can't control your toothbrush well. First of all, if you
sleep well and keep track of your schedule, there
shouldn't be a big problem with only the grooves coming out of your body. It
depends on whether the ketosis state of the bull is maintained or if you eat a gift.
Ah, if you're not in a state of ketosis and suddenly fast, I
think your body will come out more and go into a state of tension.
Ah, and I don't think you're always metabolizing carbohydrates, but I'll
do 4 or 5. You
said to eat without thinking about calories, but I don't know how much fat to eat, so
someone asked me to eat 50g or 100g for 150 won, in a ratio of 1:2:7.
Would it be okay to eat this much? I was eating about 30g more, but I
couldn't finish it there. So,
please help me with how much I should eat, considering the condition of the Yang Ji-won performance. I
think learning 1:2:7 isn't bad.
I'm trying to
consume the same number of grams of pure protein as my body weight in pounds, and I set a target protein intake
and a
rough estimate of 20% to 30% of my total calorie intake.
For example, if I eat
45kg of protein, let's put it simply. If I
weigh 45kg, that's 100 pounds,
so I try to eat as much protein as I commented. "As much protein as I
commented on is a little under 500g." Oh, and multiplying by 5, you
can see that about 20% of the meat is protein. If it's a song with a lot of fat, you
don't have to worry about fat-free outs or anything like that, but if you think about it, it's somewhere with some fat, so
9.5  Since you can see protein at about 10%, I try to eat about 500g of lean meat.
Then, I
have to calculate how much fat is in that lean meat.
If you use an application like Pass Krishna and look at it that way,
that fat is, well,
for example, if that song says 10%, if I
eat 500g of meat, I'm consuming 50g of fat.
If I want to eat 7g of fat and 3g of protein,
the total amount of fat and protein intake should be the same.
Right now, I'm eating 100g of protein, so 50g of fat is 10%, so I just
need to consume an additional 50g on top of the 50g I'm eating.
But on the other hand, if I
eat like that, the calories are exactly 100g of fat and 100g of protein,
right? If I cry when I get a bruise, it's
900 calories.  400 calories more than 1300 calories,
300 calories solid, is too little for any person. Some
people are confused about the basal metabolic rate and such for Homo sapiens, but if you
just live quietly
and consume energy at a normal, healthy rate, it exceeds 2000 calories.
Of course, if you just lie in bed and
do nothing, it wouldn't be like that, but if you live a normal life,
well, I don't necessarily want to tell you to hit 2000 calories exactly, but I
think it's good to eat a little more. If you
eat clean, you
can eat 8 calories of fat and 2 calories of protein. If you plan to eat this, multiply the amount of fat by the amount of protein.
I'm eating 100g of plums and onions right now, so that's 200g of fat.
So, I'd add 150g of fat.
There's a way to eat like that, but you don't eat that much fat. I'm not
someone who normally eats a high-fat diet, so I can tell people who are still on a high-fat diet to listen to this.
Eating 1:1 means eating that much more.
In the past, if you had cancer, you would
eat butter and drink Kongkong Baekgom Samgyeopsal, and things like that. It was popular, but it's
not like that these days. In
those cases,
adding more baggage rather than adding more fat
can be a solution. Adding 100g in 3 phases can add more calories, right?
If you think about it that way, protein calories
are this much, so about
30% of Zippo's now, but I
think you can think of it like this according to your body weight.
Hello, kind Lisa. Hello, Sarang Cham. I
went to a nice hospital and found that my lungs were clogged with phlegm, but I didn't really get it, and my throat
feels itchy. I can't sleep at night because of the saliva. I
wonder if something like propolis would help. I wonder if taking a taxi that we take and drinking it would help. I'm
thoroughly eating at a restaurant.
Oregano oil capsules can also help. I do
n't know much about propolis. I don't know exactly what propolis does,
what ingredients it contains, and what the ingredients are.
But  Well, now that spring is here,
if you're experiencing seasonal allergies, such as phlegm,
then local supplements can help.
4 Local supplements are really local, so you need to eat the pollen
produced by bees that eat the pollen around you that's bothering you.
Imported bee larvae or propolis
won't help.
4. Try eating a snack. You'll be able to sleep better.
If it gets worse when you break your fast, it could be due to the umbrella spot. You
can also try adding some Mokso Sangyeom to your diet. I
had elbow pain, so I went to the hospital and was prescribed a painkiller called Tencel. I
'm taking it as my first dose. They said it lasts a long time, but I'm
not sure if it's right to keep taking it. I didn't get hurt, so I
wonder if it's not 3 stomach measurements.
Try taking the amount produced to see if your symptoms are normal. Oh, you can tell.
Taking painkillers and anti-inflammatory medication for a long time is not good. Of course, it
thins the intestinal mucosa and causes intestinal irritation.
Wow, now, non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) are
really bad,
right? Yes, so I
think it's better to avoid those kinds of drugs.
4.
If it's because of that priority, try taking them and
see if the payment is getting better. If it's not because of you, then it's
still good to have joint pain now.
3. As you mentioned, dairy products that haven't changed much are
good.
Trying to eat even a small piece of cheese might help. Try taking
more Tamin Kate. They
say you should eat less meat and dairy during
pregnancy. I have a daughter, so I want to hear about it here too. It's really nonsense to reduce eggs and hair during breakfast and dinner. I do
n't know if you have any basis for that, but GM
says that soybeans are not related to precocious puberty unless you have a cold sore. I
think people who talk like that are no different from criminals.
Ahhh, one more.
Look at the ancestors. I
don't know if I lost the video.
Here's how much estrogen is in it. I
've shown you a table like this, quoting from the Buddhist scriptures, for your convenience. I gave you this on the air about the book.
These are foods that contain a lot of estrogen, which can cause precocious puberty.
Next, the estrogen content in the human body at each stage of life.
Oh,
regardless of gender,
before the onset of secondary sexual characteristics, children and men, regardless of gender. Let's just say that
children
divide 41,000 by about gram. Then,
estrogen is produced in both women and men.
Since s-testosterone is produced, estrogen is converted into an element by the aromatase factor. It's
just unconditionally female and unconditionally male. This kind of
thing is a bit dry. Anyway,
136,000. Next, pregnant women, 513,000, pregnant
women, 19 million, and also 19.6 million.
And here, if you look below, 5g 2
pro first, hormone-free consumption crows that didn't match the lower 5g.
And then we put in some mold and
some mycotoxins like estrogen, and we inject the 4th estrogen extracted from the mold yesterday into
the stomach and quickly put it in like this.
Then, the mold in the smoky one continues to pack so much so that the body has a
lot of estrogen and gains weight easily. American cows in particular
do this. Oh, really? The ovaries are meat. This is
n't blood, it's just meat. She has 5g of twisted meat, and the
cow that's right on the road is standing on a cedar tree.
There's 15 or crab meat on the tree, and butter is a little more on the east side of the fat, so it has
g. It has 5g of eggs that you should avoid during the month of the year. The
units change from then on. Up to here, it
's okay to look at.
This is based on 500g, but here, it's based on 500g,
right? E107  Kang Ki-jeong, huh?
200g, 227g, or
227g?
But what about bread?
Of course, there are people who eat it every day. Illustration: Human story. Fight estrogens
or gen estrogens.
Our intestinal bacteria can process them. And since it's not directly tested in the blood, there are
some unique people in this intestine. If the intestines are healthy, they
can give it to you. So, lignin and such are
much more easily broken down than isoflavones and such. So,
sesame seeds and you guys, lignin lignan, don't you hear? Because
it's a 2nd class C. Anyway, will it work? Fight estrogens are very diverse, but Hong
didn't make them. They're meant to be eaten. There's also pomegranate, and it
can break it down to some extent.
So, this much is okay. Most beans are okay, but soybeans
don't do this in large units. There's
no room for type. If you eat even a fingernail-sized amount, it's
like eating soy sauce. You do it for a year straight, and so on.  So unless you eat it, soy
sauce actually has almost no phytoestrogens.
And we don't eat a lot of soy sauce, so we don't eat it with soy sauce before. We
don't drink soy sauce like this.
4 If we just eat the cover,
what kind of thing is it? Eating eggs and eggs on the 4th day
causes precocious puberty. That's crazy. Are you crazy?
Or are you just a chick? Anyway, it's going.
Hello, Navy Tyre.
4 It's nonsense.
Even
in China,
traditionally, children would never eat this. Even
adults didn't eat much of it.
Yes, it doesn't make sense for children to eat it.
Oh, come to think of it, I was eating some blueberries, and I think my
mouth hurt.
4 I went to eat some bells.
What's the difference between the Pali group and the Khan button? The
825 diet that people usually talk about is
really, really different from the lecture format.
To sell. Of course, now that there are famous people in the 825 field,
each of them has a slightly different opinion.
What's selling?  Although the discussion differs slightly, the
basic idea behind the Paleolithic diet is to
eat like people in the Paleolithic era. The basis for this is
based on archaeological evidence, is
n't there a lot of archaeological evidence?
People who consider the Paleolithic diet often
think about what ancient people would have eaten, and they often do so out of thin air.
Back then, people didn't farm, so they
couldn't eat grains. So, before we started farming and raising livestock, we
didn't grow grapes. So, how much food would we have had? There
would have been very little. And we shouldn't eat parts of the plant.
So, what did ancient people eat? They would have
hunted animals,
eaten fruit from trees, eaten any kind of fruit, and
eaten various vegetables found in the wild. This is the
mindset of people on the 825 diet.
And the 825 Daitan people, especially Dr. Laurent Codding, has
studied the Red-Eyed Tribes of today and studied the modern-day Thrivers.
I
often think about how the tribal tribes ate, and how Simon would have assumed that this
would be the original restaurant we ate at. The percentage of animal foods in the current primitive population is calculated from various factors. For
example, tribe A, called the "Talisman C" tribe, and the structure F, they
averaged out zinc intake. Therefore, to be
healthy, we should eat a certain amount of plant foods. Beyond that, we should eat a certain amount of good food.
People ate this much fruit, so we should eat about this much fruit.
However, most of the meat we hunt these days is from wild animals.
Look at the animals. They don't have much fat, so they have to decorate their houses.
There are many problems with this kind of storytelling process. First of all, people in the past
couldn't eat grains, but they ate grains. This
doesn't mean grains were like this and then stopped. Whether grains or grains are
seeds, they contain the same amount of nutrients and have the same protective defense mechanisms.
We need to neutralize them. There's no difference whether we eat grains or nuts.
So, unconditionally, tortillas are bad, and unconditionally, nuts are bad.  People in the past ate it or
not. This itself was very difficult to avoid.
And the environment in which hunter-gatherer tribes live is
very different from that of people 300 years ago, just 100 years ago. It goes without saying that the environment of people living in a company 300 years ago is very different. 10,000 years
ago, 20,000 years ago, 10,000 years ago, it goes without saying that
humans faced a period of great upheaval between 10,000 years ago and 100,000 years ago.
From that time on, in order to survive, the
ice age ended and the great bang came. It
was like that. Until 10,000 years ago, there was still an ice age, and animals were very large. So, there wouldn't have been as many fruits as there are now, and
plants wouldn't have grown as much. And the animals that lived at that time, as
animals grew larger, they just grew larger, so their
fat didn't increase proportionally to their size. For example, a 100 kg
animal all shouting out that they have 10% body fat would be the same as a 100 kg animal's body
fat.  A
500 kg animal would have 10 kg of
body fat, but that's not the case anymore. Let's say a 500 kg animal has 10 kg of body fat. A 500
kg animal has 20% body fat. The
bigger it gets, the more fat it has. This sparrow graph shows.
Yes, is it a
beheading? Since it shows on a log scale like this,
people in the past would have been much better at eating fat than they do now. They would
have eaten more fat if they
hunted larger animals. The reason we don't have fat when we hunt animals now is because we've eliminated all the large animals.
Now, especially, the Haja tribe, who Dr. Laurent Coding makes a lot of dolls,
now depends almost entirely on the baobab tree for their diet. Relying on the baobab tree
means eating the baobab fruit that grows on the baobab tree and the forage in the
fields that make up the baobab tree. They depend on a lot of calories from those things,
but until just a few hundred years ago,  There are too many elephants in Africa, and
if they just sit still, the baobab trees can't survive. Elephants will immediately go to the
Canadian bush to drink the
water, because the trees have a lot of water, so they
like to fall down the baobab trees and drink the water inside.
That's how we humans have recently been slaughtering elephants and
killing all the elephants, so we've seen a lot of baobab trees.
In the past, people who hunted and ate elephants killed the giraffes, and the chestnut trees have become abundant, so elephants are
eating a lot of baobab trees. When they come out of the baobab tree, they
depend on it. This is what people in the past ate, and
it's very work-related,
so now
there are a lot of things like this that Fisher Lek is attracted to.
There are a lot of differences, but the general cami and router are a little bit. 1 and 2 are just chapters 1 and 2. It's cute.
Even if you pour it, it doesn't grow all like this. 2 is simple. It's a
plant-based supermarket. What is Khan? It's eating everything from animal products.  It
has absolutely nothing to do with that kind of thing. There's a
difference between that kind of borrowing and the 4th verse ceremony. You
can think of it as foreign news from what I said.
If you suppress it, you work as a nurse, but when you dance during the day, your legs get numb. Uruk, please
scream and sergeant, right leg, thigh, ankle, etc.
Are there any 0.2 foods that can help you?
Eat a lot of salt and
[music]
like gold. If you eat it consistently with eta in the fall, it's like a
dog. Eat a lot of citrus inner, and
then take an action salt bath. It means enough. After that, you
seem to have insulin resistance. If you work at night, it's almost
impossible to not feel a sharp pain. It's just
that the carcinogen classification divided by WHO is
written as a Group 1 carcinogen, so now it's
nonsense. It's not well-provided, but it's designated by people who don't provide it well.
Anyway, now, what's called a carcinogen at night? It's
not just that it's designated as a child, it's actually incredibly bad.
What I said to suppress this wind might not be enough.
Working on cancer means you have to
give up your health. It's a
shame that some people have to work at night,
but there's a particularly bad person in England called Elliot 5 Button.
So now, when accepting patients, they
don't accept people who work at night.
They probably think that their health can't improve because of the night anyway,
so they think that the effects will only become apparent now.
Of course, it's not like they have to be sick for the rest of their lives, but I
can try my best. In any case,
if you have insulin resistance, it's
bad. Even if you supplement with electrolytes and eat more, the
21st century itself blocks the entry of thallium into the cells.
Salt is contained in the salt itself. So, eating a lot of salt
doesn't solve the problem significantly.
The salt is already stuck in the cells and doesn't move. Eating a little more
can cause swelling due to the heat.
In this way, now, you should do your best to eat at a restaurant and turn off the
light when you sleep at night.
In a state where you
can sleep in complete darkness, and then even in that state,
try to live regularly and do as many healthy things as possible with the help of various other people, but you
still have to give up your superiors. In fact, this kind of thing doesn't make sense in a natural state. Please be
good at night. If
we think of the tent as animals living outside in the wild,
there are these pains and such.
How much can a 25kg child eat? Currently, I'm alternating between ostrich and
breast milk cams at 30g per day.
The child has a rabbit, is short, and has a bad back. I'm going deep now and always eating
egg yolk and vitamin D care. What should I take more?
As for the current level, I think it's enough. My sheep
has atopic dermatitis, is short, and has poor eyesight. I'll see you recently. Egg yolk, vitamin
D supplements. If you do that, you
won't need to take additional Park. The
chairman eats it, and we mean it. On the other hand, this is okay,
but I eat it.
So now it's the shortest and best liver.  What's the story?
Egg yolk. Egg yolk and a little more bone-sparing things like that can be added.
Occasionally, seafood is also given once
in a while. If the yolk doesn't improve, foods that can cause inflammation are 2. Egg yolk may be a common cause of dermatitis, or it may be milk, so if it doesn't improve, try removing it. You have to continue giving it consistently. Vitamin A and arachidonic acid, which are abundant in the liver, will
help the immune system not react to certain foods,
so if you pay attention to these, I think you should take it slow now.
However, the eyes may not recover. Height
can grow if you eat meat well from now on,
but in fact,
many factors are determined when the baby is born. If
the baby eats well from now on, the baby can live as healthy as possible now and be
born healthier later. But in fact,
there are some things that can't be helped. A lot is determined at birth,
so in the old days, the people of the primitive land carefully prepared during pregnancy.
People usually just eat healthy every day, but  When trying to get pregnant, there was a special
preparation period, and
until the baby was born and raised, I continued to take care of it. Genji Taye, yes,
later on, there are many things that cannot be undone. It would be good
if it got better, but you have to
keep in mind that it can come. You
can't take painkillers.
Painkillers just make you numb the pain. If you suspect that it's a symptom of a pastor's 4-year discharge, you
should take Oksa's welcome g.
Yes, pastor, you can take it. It's because of the captain's discharge, and it stops sooner than you think.
It's not because of the clothes, and you have to quickly find another cause. Also, if the pain
doesn't stop, sugar should be a painkiller. There may be things like that, but
when you suspect that it's because of the madam, it's the
fastest
way to see the meaning of the rooftop sentence. Even if you think, "Is this because of the Osan point?" I can't tell you that it's because of the 9th episode and 4 years. You have no choice but to check for yourself. The thing about
eggs and such is
ridiculous. Seriously, that's ridiculous. When
I go out, I mean,
when I have an autoimmune disorder, what foods do I react to?  If you know the answer, you
can add 1 even if it's embarrassing. If it can be managed well,
but in an uncertain situation, it's best to exclude everything and
try it. You
can try eating Roma for a few months and then add egg yolk. In particular, people who have had 110 for
less than 6 months are advised not to eat eggs. In the myth, 8ml is also said to do so. Since
eggs have a lot of cholesterol, cholesterol is the first to go to the sexes, so if you think that sexual hormones will be
insufficient and sexual eczema will occur, it's
amazing. Kwon In-ha,
guide. Hello, my
child is heading towards a new name, so this product is a dog, but it was a point. Young Chicago,
after 3 years of humiliation in the yard, good constitution, good egg yolk, there is no change. It's
really amazing. Yes,
those things disappear. As time passes, silver is cut g.
Well, time passes. The antibodies that react to the child's delayed allergy take
some time to stabilize. It doesn't get better just by waiting quietly during that time.
He or she should try again.  How to know if perfectly good food will cause an inflammatory reaction  It's
important to invest in the opi tamae and the cherished Sanschi company that prevents adverse reactions,
but it's
good now, but it takes time.
Oh, or is it okay? The one sold on the market said it was 100% undead ken fishing boat.
If it's not good, I'm going to stop. Ato is
blown. Of course, it would be much better from the beginning in terms of safety and such,
but
I don't think there's any need to take action. I do
n't think there's anything good to eat. I don't know if the toxins in soybeans are completely detoxified, and I think it's best to avoid any soybean or soybean food at all costs. I don't think there's a single b in hand.
4. In
other words, I think meat and eggs must have had a lot of growth promoters
and antibiotics in these products. You know, meat and eggs have almost no growth promoters or
antibiotics. That's all a lie. I'm not in favor of using growth promoters and antibiotics in raising animals, and I do
n't think there are many people who are as critical as I am. But that doesn't mean there's anything wrong with it.
Meat suddenly has a lot of growth promoters and antibiotics in it.
No, that's not true.
Of course, that's not good, but it's right not to use it.
The clamp set used in the feed that meat families eat is really, really bad. It should
never happen and should disappear in the future. But there's a
good reason for that now. Meat is cut. There are
too many antibiotics and growth promoters, and it's
dangerous to the point where it's not related to soybeans, but they're not the main culprit in precocious puberty. It's
all more so than you think. Suddenly, I said, "
Meat is unconditionally good and all politics are
bad." But you might think that way, but
when you look at the data, as you can see in the pictures I posted here, the
cows that were given hormones are also
tree g, and the eggs shown there are just garbage, sweet ones that you can get from somewhere.
Yes, it's not like that.
In situations where we really have no choice, we can live healthy enough by eating meat that's completely garbage.
Of course, it's true that there are people who are so sensitive that we should even change that to pasture-raised meat.
But in general, as we talked about today,
meat and eggs are used to modify puberty.  What do you need to be careful about?
In any situation, unless it's
something so foreign that you can't even imagine raising OT in some really strange third-world country within our country, you
don't have to worry about consuming livestock products that are legally distributed in our country. As far as
I know, there isn't a translated version of the Caliber book. I
think it will come out soon. Translation isn't that difficult,
so if translators become
more interested, I think they'll come out one by one. The
reason why the Nito book, which hadn't been published for a while, started coming out once is because it's been extended.
What should I do if I have rhinitis?
I saw the 4 and in what situation it occurred. I don't know what you
're eating right now, what your lifestyle habits are, or whether you've seen a converter.
But in general, since it's just inflammation, ultimately,
it's helpful to remove the cause of inflammation. Things
like fasting can also help. I
talked about the 4000 today, and activities that can boost the clutch, such as
eating foods, will help.
Today,  We didn't talk about it, but
there's another source of glutathione in food, raw milk.
Of course, I have raw egg whites, and I have some raw egg whites at home,
so I'm not in a position to recommend them, but if you
eat them separately from the egg yolk and the
egg white, or if you don't eat egg whites continuously from morning to night, there
may not be a big problem. If you
eat them separately and eat them with meals that you don't eat, you
can eat plenty of Beauty 4. So, I think there
won't be a problem with our method. Now, I'm taking advantage of the pressure,
so eating raw egg whites can be helpful for boosting your immune system. What do you mean,
cysteine, etc. are different, so
I think it would be good to try those things? In the
case of eggs, do you have to check if you haven't seen them before before buying them? The script is important, but
there are many other important things besides what I turned off. I'm talking about burner number 1.  It's not all good,
so getting vaccinated and making eggs is only 2 points, so I'm speaking generally.
Since the vaccine's child often has an album, the liquid album, empty
yes, fruit and vegetable victims often investigate directly, so if
the dream is so dirty, it's because the immune response is
trying to induce a strong immune response.
If you walk, it can now cause an allergic reaction to eggs. If
even one of the art symbols in what we eat is known, can I feed the rich? I do
n't know how much you mean by unlimited. Linoleic acid
can be excessive.
So, in this case, is it okay even if it's not good quality?
When considering health, if we don't have good quality meat, it's a bit of a problem. What about quality?
What do we think is ideal? It
doesn't have to be meat. There's no substitute for it. I told
you earlier that there's no room.
Black copycatting is now less. Meat is soaked in mussels, so I'm following it very slowly.
Peaceful torpedoes, especially the degree of fat, butter, a cup of coffee
at home, a cushion cup every day, and other fat. Intentionally punishing to eat to force.  I'm
eating a little bit of lard mixed with fat and eaten by middle school students,
but for no reason, it keeps changing, especially like a positive.
First,
how much fat are you eating in grams? Are you
eating close to twice the amount of protein? Also,
take a look at the grams. That's more helpful than you think. I do
n't think you can get a good sense of it with the general public,
so I recommend you try it.
And not drinking coffee can help. If you drink coffee,
of course, you've had it before, so you're probably still drinking coffee,
or now,
yes, I'm very negative about coke, and
even if you do a 5k, it
seems better to eat it with rice, but I mean, starting in the morning,
when you start the fall group, that's not so good.
Yes, you do
more, but it's not good, and wouldn't it be better to breathe out the opi?
Yes, I have a video of the coffee. I told you not to drink coffee.
Oh, that's right.
Sometimes, you can drink fragrant coffee, but drinking it every day is the
same as a drug. The
mechanism of action of the image quality opponent is
attached, and there are side effects, too.  This seems to be the case.
There's a difference of this level. What kind of harm is it? It's the same. That's
not what I'm trying to say.
So, sometimes it's better to cut down on coffee. There's a video about this, too.
Yes, there's
something like this. Since it contains so much caffeine, if you
drink it like this, the half-life of caffeine is very long. It's the time it takes for caffeine to be absorbed, and this half-life means that if it's halved,
it's a big half-life. In
other words, if you
drink one Asics or Red Bull, you can consume 60mg of caffeine, but if you
drink a Starbucks Americano, you'll consume
150mg. If you drink a Starbucks Americano at 12:00 PM, thinking, "Oh, it's lunchtime, let's have a cup of coffee and wake up," and if you drink it at 6 PM, you'll have 4 more caffeine circulating in your body than if you drink a Hot Six or Red Bull.
Because of the Starbucks Americano you had for lunch, you'll
have 4 more caffeine than the notice. So,
coffee is
not good for sightseeing, and
because you walked.  Yes, it's not a power trip.
It's because of society that there are a lot of omega sixes and low omega repairs. 4. You can make eggs with a lot of omega threes and low omega sixes. For example, if you feed them a
lot of fish with a lot of omega threes and almost no omega 6m, or
feed them a lot of mama c with a lot of alpha linolenic acid, then you'll have a lot of mice.
And the eggs will taste like fish,
so people won't eat them.
Yes, there are things like that. It's not difficult.
Let's make eggs like this. It'll be expensive, right? If you eat fish, the price will go up dramatically. But now, even if it's expensive, you can make eggs with a lot of omega threes.
But now, the eggs will taste like fish. It's not an event. The reason it tastes like fish is because
omega threes play a big role.
2. Eating meat fed the 4th class is that kind of
grain-based d ring 4. It's like this.
Yes, if you eat meat with that style, it really shows. Of course, the meat-
eating class that ate meat ate meat and said that the meat smelled bad, but the
opposite seems to be the same.
Ramen or fast food is the same.  Is that not possible? That's why I don't eat them at all. How to
choose eggs? I have a blog post about how to choose a dog. It's titled "How to choose a really good egg, right?" If you
type this, the blog will probably come up. There's a
post called "How to choose a really good egg" in the category of "Restaurant Thoughts."
Here, I'll go over
some of the things to consider when choosing eggs.
This would be the best, but we don't have anything like this in our country. Since there's no one that
grows eggs in this environment, well,
yeah, even if
bass isn't available right now, you can choose the next best option.
There are plenty of good eggs. It's
a bit of a Maginot Line, but it
would be nice if paper-free eggs could be found on the market. I'm
being thorough. White fish is fine, but red meat and blue fish are boring. It's like a
zombie school. It's only right that we have to do
it. Look at your body. Seafood can be like that. In
that case, it's better to eat it.
We don't have a short history of eating samosa,
so I don't know how to fix it.
Hello, Wangseong Kim. It's your first time chatting. So,
for now.  Do you want to do it? You can ask questions anytime. I
live in the intelligent world, and last year, my son caught the genre capital. It seems to be immune. I was
so scared and happy when I found an article in this app that helped me. I was only making money, so I was happy. I
live in the Sydney area. My name
is Dr. Paul Mason. I gave an introduction to you, Jikim.
Then,
okay. After Lee came out, there was
no chat right now. Anyway, I
don't remember exactly where I was going crazy, but if you look it up now, you'll
find out where I'm cleansing.
2 minutes. A specialist in autoimmune diseases. This section treats the weaker parts.
I hope you visit. Um, the
department is a farmer. Hello.
When I was young, I used to eat raw eggs with chopsticks, but I used to
eat a lot of those things. It's a bit humane. It's used a lot in law.
If you catch a cold, you can see what it is.
It's quite effective. I think it's 4002, so I think it's effective. I wonder if it'll
go away.  I think so.
Since there's Drucker in the living room, they must have eaten it like that in the past. And
yes, eggs themselves are very nutritious food. 5.
In the beginning, would you buy eggs only for the data without considering the same thing?
Do you have to say the purpose?
Oh, I still recommend eating eggs that have a raw certification. Wow,
those that only have antibiotic certification don't get much praise. There
are many cheap eggs that have antibiotics, so
if you're considering 1, I think it's better to stick to antibiotic-free ones.
Of course, you can eat cheap eggs, but now I
think my body will naturally get better if I eat the best ingredients possible.
Yes, it's hard to expect that I'm healthy if I eat unhealthy food.
But that's also very closely related to sincerity.
So, if you ride a $2 car that's bursting, and wear a can, a lot of the bones will
disappear.
If they don't disappear, well, I think the book
was often mentioned on TV, but you cover your mouth like this and
put tape on your mouth like this. It's called mouth taping.
There's something called putting tape on your mouth and sleeping. Of course, there are those with sleep apnea.  For
those who snore, if you change your mouth and sleep, you might
get an offer. It
seems like the lime keeps falling out, but anyway, you
might be thinking, "If you keep your mouth shut, won't you just grow and die?" I
used to think that way too. I also have a really stuffy nose, and I'm using Mishima Goma,
but I
sleep better than I thought even after putting a tape on it.
4 That helps a lot. Well, it
feels like a bit of a drastic prescription, but it's
really bad for your body to breathe through your mouth when you sleep with chocolate cancer. It prevents you from getting a deep sleep.
4 Putting a detector in your mouth and sleeping
is a helpful item.
Of course, I didn't have any children, but
yes, that's something like 4 testimony. It's not
common, but people who talk about it say that it's not a stomach. Please tape your mouth. If
you come again because there's no distance between your noses, your apnea will disappear. There are a lot of things like that.
In a book like the strongest diet, it says that the body has a lot of omega-3 fatty acids and inflammation.
What should I do?
Until the mother's six disappears, how do I eat the minimum without eating more?  It is said that
taking an additional 10 IU each time can be helpful.
During that time,
5 people each have a 3 half-life of about 601, so if you can
endure M5 rock for about 10 years, you will
be very happy. However, if you eat a lot of stearic acid during that time, Mom Six
will accelerate the speed a bit, as they say.
According to that ball Saladin,
people have seen it in their clinical practice, so that could be helpful. I
saw the 2D dot.
Ja 8 Yes, this
came out. Kang Dae-seong,
uh,
4 CD. Concord side,
omega-3 eggs. My dietary pattern is to eat a lot of vegetables.
Um, there are books that tell you not to read a lot, and
there are books that I want, but the strongest diet is not to eat a lot of just anything.
It tells you to be careful and eat carefully.
4 Oxygen points are removed like this, and
broccoli and these things are cooked and eaten without
knowing it. The first
floor doesn't come out. I wake up without sleeping. The solid is
our 2
first.  I said it
was a bit more comfortable because I had to match the speed and moon with me.
In the past, I used to go to construction sites and work in
the fields and do that. Um,
yes, I
recently bought Cheongnan, and assuming that the Seol Kang-kyung-hee is the same, is Cheongnan significantly more
nutritious than regular oil? It seems like that.
As far as I know, there is
no difference.
But now, Cheongnan is similar to the top.
1. It may not be the same, but there will be no difference for the sake of it.
2.
Eat more grass, and the eggs are bigger. I don't know, but 1.
Is it still on TV?
It feels like it's been caught and pulled out.
Anyway, 10 million. I don't know if what you're saying is better. I haven't
really compared it like that. There's no
effect. It's the author of Potter below.
Chickens can catch more and actually fall even further.
Usually, these eggs are bigger.
Generally speaking, if the chicken eats more and the eggs are bigger, you can
think of it as having more English.
If the chicken is weak, assuming that the society is good,
then eat a lot and
then open it.  I've been eating a lot of rice lately,
but I don't get much acne here, but I think it's because I have a slight inflammatory reaction around my temples. I've
had this since I was little. I've had acne on this side lately, but these days, when
I eat rice with a friend, my friend
can't eat a lot of fat without rice, so if there's
chestnuts, she eats well. Dad, I think it's good for Nepalese
people who eat a lot of fat to eat a spoonful of rice.
So we ate a lot of rice together, but
these days, more acne is growing at the bottom, so I was thinking about not eating, but
right now, all the fat is gone, so I'm going
to use the side fat medicine every day next Monday, but
I think I need to put some in until then. I
'm eating it together because it's fat that comes from the mountains, but
amh 2
um,
Israel subtract, isn't it the same Cargill venture? I do
n't think there will be any. As far as I know, Cargill doesn't use Excel, so it's okay. I
know about 2 eks.
Anyway, acne is on the neck.  I don't think the person with the lower jaw is very sensitive. If you eat tangerines at that time, you'll
really lose weight.
Tangerines or oranges, or a little bit of citrus, I'm
really sorry.
Hong Kong, Cornell Becks, Benz, please write a personal letter. My husband is trying to hit me, but I'm trying to stop him.
Is there a plan to reorganize the industry?
I don't know. I think there's something being suggested in Fashion Play 3,
but it
would be important to just close all the restaurants and such.
Researchers now have 100 wins at Cornell. If you can speak
English, you can do it online. Since I
see a lot of patients online, including foreigners, British, Australians, and Americans, these days,
people with weaker functions may not come to the clinic in person,
so I
spread it more online. I often do it over the phone or something like that.
Hello, nice to meet you. The line is Hello.
Chelsea Jang's tsk is
different, so when I saw it, it's a bit of a Korean accent. It's not that I don't have children,
but it seems close to a native speaker, so I'm not sure if I should say
something like, "If you have Korean blood in your children, give them some rice." I've
seen it before.
Burlesque's Seol lost more weight, and
then lost 5 kilos as water intake decreased. At first, I ate a low-carb diet like this, and after that, when I went to Ireland, I was like, "Is it real?" I couldn't eat a super high-calorie diet, so I stubbornly ate over 5,000 calories a day and gained some weight.
Then, I stopped eating like that, so I drank a little.
These days, I'm working out hard and putting on some weight.
I got a call from my father, so I should come to Toggle.
Um, it's long.
Scar is a common delivery machine. Hello, I saw the
problem. While doing it, the end is also
Jeongman 4. Is it better? I do
n't think it's unnecessary to buy expensive things. You know, it's
better to buy it even if it's expensive, right? Is that right? I guess there's a
difference. It's shabby. It's smaller, so it seems dirty.
Yes, it seems like it would be okay. Just
think of it like that instead of the yolk and the egg, Congressman Scott. Don't think about it too much.
Albolo. Now, as chickens get older, their eggs get bigger, and that's because they have a
lot of nutrients. I don't know for sure, but it's not necessarily because they have a lot of mobile eggs.
Anything will be right. As the eggs grow, they
come out occasionally, so putting them in occasionally will also increase the amount. When they
come out once every two days, it may not be 2 times 2, but it may not be 1.5, but it
will increase anyway.
Yes, if you
do well and then explore, what will happen when sugary foods come up? When you
raise them,
if you think you have to eat them, you really have to do it. Ah, when they are
young, you have to think of other ways, but if it's just carrots, that's
not right.
Books.
Oh, please write a book. I don't think
I'm good enough to write a book.
No, there are no books. I'm not qualified to write a book, but I have
time and I do
n't have much work.
Yes, there are people who write books well. Writing well means writing really well.
Aside from that, there are people who write
books whenever they have time and publish them several times.
There are people who write books 15 times in 10 years. Those people do
n't have that tendency, and
translating a book that can be washed and dried seems too difficult. Even if it's a
pill,
not many people will read it, so Dr. Surprise's book is actually more for native English speakers.  I have
n't seen it because it's such an old book,
I think only about a percent of our cafe members and
YouTube subscribers have searched for it since it's been popular.
Yes, it's
transparent, but if there's no particular reason to turn off the carbon, you don't have to.
As Euphoria said, the baby was wrong for almost 16 months, and my husband did
n't eat elasticity, so isn't that why? I
didn't know that it was an oboro bond. Should I give the baby ginseng that has muscles? It's not
because the elasticity doesn't come out well in the west, right? 9 10 6 months is enough to
eat a little bit of silver bullet fight, but since
there are almost no files and bombs, it's fine.
4 She's doing exploration and not knowing, it's not necessary. It's
not true that it uses muscle glycogen and things like that. It seems like the baby will use up muscle glycogen and
use up strength so hard, but
the amount of muscle glycogen is what Khan sees, so exploration is really almost like
people in Ambong, except for the very small amount contained in meat.
Yours  There's no difference between people who eat a lot and fight.
There's no difference in recovery.
Well, I don't know about walking. It's hard to say that you'll walk unconditionally when the time comes.
I don't do a lot of distribution,
so if you talk to other experts, you'll know if I'm
eating 16 and it's too late or if it's worth waiting. I do
n't have a sense of timing. It's
not acne, but my skin is really red. Anyway, I haven't used it yet. I
smoke 7 inches and Mindy
doesn't have epilepsy, but it's too much to call it a house. It's like 8 and then it
's red and 5 degrees. Is it an
allergy, or is it because of the Quest Tamin, or is it an
autoimmune reaction?
Try checking each of those things one by one. I think it will work. Check if there's something you're lacking or eating normally. I
think it would be helpful to look at it once to see if there's anything you're lacking. Just what's completely empty? What's wrong with eating like that, but your
skin is a bit dry.  There seems to be a problem, and when it seems like there might be a problem separately,
supplementing with vitamin C can be helpful.
As I mentioned earlier, when we're talking about the long-term side of Korean folk songs, we
avoid eating
meat, but since the vitamin C in it is lacking, it
may not be enough, and the degree of oxidative stress varies from person to person,
so 3. Vitamin C deficiency can cause problems, and yes,
there are
things like that, and
eating more glutathione 2.
Insulin works hard, so it
might be helpful to make it more utilized. If
Tom does it, how much vegetable kimchi would you like? How many grams would you like to have
before treatment? It seems like it's been too long since I ate cancer treatment. It's really
good.
Sometimes, when I go out and eat something like an overnight stay, if there's
something in it, I just eat it.
But other than that,
I follow the vegetables and put them in the island quality, or when the side dishes come out, I put them
in something.
That's not true, it
's been a really long time. Even if I say it's been a really long time, it's only been a few years, so I guess I
can talk about it to that extent. No, no. Anyway,
I wanted to do this,
but before I thought about it, it wasn't that difficult. Changing restaurants wasn't that difficult.
But in my case, I
know that many people have a hard time with this, and I
know that I'm a special case who can change things so easily, so I do
n't think I can give any major advice about that. I
think there's something like that.
Of course, when I see a food, I've eaten it before, so I
don't often get hooked on it and say it looks delicious. When we first see a food, we
picture it in our heads, and we think, "Wow, that looks really delicious." And
today, processed foods and such are mostly things we've already eaten,
so when it goes into our mouths, we think, "Oh, this is going to be really delicious."
When we smell it, we crave it, and things like that. We also have dinner here,
but I've learned a lot about how the Hamsik Garden has been bad for a long time and have to
endure it.  As I was going, I felt like my mind was completely
blown away.
So, I think the saying, "A little knowledge is power," might be applicable in situations like this. It
might be helpful to know a little more clearly why I'm trying to avoid those foods and how those foods will affect my current goals.
Yesterday's episode, "
The Fat Is Now Free-Range," showed that the food was quite varied. Three
might be a bit lacking, but this company said they eat it once or
twice a week. It means that they have enough Omega-3s, and if the
DJ says he'll
never eat seafood,
it's better to eat these things once in a while. Should I
remove it? What about eggs with a yellowish tint?
Then I don't think it really matters. Unwashed ones are
better. But
in three factories, washing is a bit like that. I
have to do it here. I eat to write a book, but I'll
blow it later. I'll sit down and earn some money.
Maybe I just don't have the motivation to walk.
A little.  How about
doing it together, like quickly hitting the old one next to you while walking?
4 I think you can do that better than me, but
I think it would be good to distribute it as a collection PDF of cafe members or something like that. To be
honest, no matter how much I talk about what's good and what's bad, it's just
not the same.
For example, let's say there's a restaurant that serves sweetfish dip. There's a place I've
never been to, a place I've never eaten, and the owner
comes out and says how delicious their house is, and how
good the ingredients are, what kind of experience I have, how much experience I've had cooking,
how much research I've done, and what high-quality ingredients they
airlifted directly from a nearby school playground or just
made themselves.
Even after the design,
there are things I hear a little bit about, right?
My Geumho Tang, it's my home cooking, so they'll say it's delicious. It's a little like that.
But now, if people around me say, "Oh, it's so delicious, it's
even more delicious," and leave a lot of good reviews, I'll be more like Hokage.
And somehow, among them, the ingredients section is actually something I can really trust.
Oh, it was really delicious.
It was delicious.
I ate it and it
was like, "Oh, I've seen it before." I think there should be something like this. And then I really believe it. I'll
just do it in the fall. If other people say it's delicious, it's really busy. I thought about it earlier.
But in that sense, even
if I try to make people think, "Isn't it open?" In the end, it's
not just the owner who talks, but other people who come forward and
talk about it. That's important.
So, I'm really grateful for the comments on the cafe's menu review board. Whether
someone writes something simple or something, it does
n't matter if you buy it
now. Those things accumulate and ultimately help spread the message to more people. So, I
think it's a huge help.
In that sense, I think I'll edit it a little better and upload it later. I
think it'd be fun to find YouTube content like this, interview them,
or meet them and
talk about it. But
I think there's something lazy about Jegal.
Ah,
the app is guiding. Nice to meet you.
Can you raise the bar for male Allah 3?  I'm
not sure if it's because of the reservation rate, but my skin was itchy.
Well, if you consider whether it's possible or not, I don't think it's impossible. Unless
there's something special in it or it's severely oxidized oil, I do
n't think it's possible. Oh, yes, first, if you
don't apply it and leave it for a while
and it gets better, and if you apply it again when it gets better, if it itches again, then it's probably because
of the nur.
Of course, you have to control variables as much as possible, but empirically,
there are many times when seeing it is surprisingly accurate. Try it.
Before that, I went to the
gym and did rate training
like this before coming to Pyeongchang. I tried to do compound exercises like compound bow blunts and debt.
Rather than working out for too long and for several hours, I
tried to go more often, even if it was short, at least four days a week and work out consistently.
But I actually think that's better than that.
There are bodyweight books like Animal Flow and Bodyweight Bookment, which use the body, right? Those are things that
emphasize Mark's Ron Balance Co., and things like that.  I
think it would be better to do mates after that becomes the basics. But whenever I talk about exercise, I always say, "
Do the exercise you like." What's good and what's
bad? The main thing is to consider that.
If it's not an exercise that I can do consistently and enjoyably, I won't do it anyway. I
said, "You should do the exercise you like. What makes you look good? I do
n't think that's very good. I don't really like exercising, so I
did weight training that was short but intense.
4. Why is it right to do an exercise you like separately? If you have a specific exercise you like, do that. Is
there
anything you need to add, such as salt water, pepper, and egg yolk? It would be good to add more bones.
Rather than saying "Nausea Joker," you should add them later. You
can't live on rice alone, so you need to
consume more cola. In that sense, you
can choose more meat, such as tendons and other things that are good for you. You can eat at other
stores, and it's 1000
1d nin.
Thank you for the 5,000 won billing. I always watch your broadcasts well. Thank you. I
don't think I've heard your nickname much, but if you tell me you watch your broadcasts well, what's
strong?
Ha, ah, it comes out.
Rather, earlier, you were always eating pizza and ice cream, but
these days, the young New Medicine people don't talk about anything strange. They
talk about their own side rules and
everything is mental. I saw this once while watching it, and
that Tory community post kept popping up. They
brought out pizza like this and asked if anyone thought this was right to come
out. They said that people who are not in their right minds said that they should eat this and that they are sane. So, I saw that there were 5 open days recently, and then there was another day, and then there was some video recommendation and it fell and I watched it, but
it's mental, so it's not in your head, but it's okay to eat. It's all okay. If you
put your body on the line, you can eat it. So, this person, after diligently eating a diet
and getting enough sleep, decided on this. Does anyone eat it? I
wonder if it's something like that.
Try eating a tan si once. Ah, the future is around 500, and the
lungs are gradually disappearing. When I was using the extractor around me, I hung up.  I randomly
came here, so I asked if it was because of the 4th episode of Private School and studied it.
Well, actually,
Tree also wasn't a singer of the Car Empire all the time. I remember doing that, but it's
not like you don't eat carbon while playing To You.
Yes, the useful exploration Tekkaman is a bit like that. So, since there
may be other problems, as the director said,
it's important to discuss things like inspections with experts and get their imaginations.
Tell me a little bit. Ah, but there seem to be a lot of interesting things. It's
really interesting to hear this from you all. People who said they were Walkie-talkies are
also very interesting. I uploaded
it as a YouTube comment and iTunes Summit post while changing to Vitamin K Tank Fur in the past, so I wonder if I
can show you this.
But I uploaded it on Channel
4 like
this.
Oh, should I say it again?
This is this. There was a tab comment. Kim Min-jun is already
20 and 5 years old, but the character is 2 cm tall. It's
not just Kim Min-ji, but also Kong, who is 27 years old.
Seriously, but
women.  Even though you're a man, there are cases where men grow a little later,
but that woman is also
2cm or 3cm taller.
Oh, after eating, the
ostrich rode high. It would be right. You have this kind of thing and other things, like
allergies disappearing and
dogs are fed raw meat, but I saw this and the chairman disappeared and the dog got sick.
Now, every time I give it to someone new, it's really
a.
Um, it's amazing. I'm just so amazed. Even if it's theoretically possible, it
feels different when you actually see it.
And even though it's theoretically possible, I didn't think about growing taller by the river, but my
25-27-year-old child is growing up with an MSC. She's
conscious of it, and she's gorgeous. She has butter, tea,
thumb, and office work. She has free lunch and dinner, and she wants to have meat, but it fluctuates depending on the radius in the evening. I
think I should buy meat and eat it in the city. Is there an appropriate way?
This weapon seems like it'll start to eat, but is it because you
can't take the military road? Is that why you're saying that?
If you're worried that your share will be hurt,
that doesn't matter.
4 It's a little late.  You can store it and drink it as is.
I don't really like butter tea, so
how about drinking it as herbal tea instead of this special second round of tea?
Cam, Mom, work, rosemary, moth, time,
verbena, right? You can
find peppermint, and other types. There are
so many leaf tea shops, and there are carpenters in them, and
so on. I
hate this. I pack a lunch and eat it when I
go to work in the fields. I don't grill
meat and bring it with me.
Everyone else packs home-cooked meals,
but that's not the case. I just eat it there. You can eat it like that.
Bring plenty of liver and fat. But now, if you cook lamb or something like that
once, the smell gets stronger. If you turn it on and let it cool, the smell gets much stronger. If you
assemble it and let it cool, the smell gets much stronger. If you sleep, you can do it
once, but it's weak. If you don't like that, I'll
buy 500 for breakfast, dinner, and dinner.  If I choose, I
'll probably end up eating a lot of English and brush my teeth.
Is there a way to solve the problem of absolute quantity and negative sentences? Ah, if you peel and
grind meat in one meal, it ends up with muscle meat, so
eating 600g is a lot. It's not much, but if you
look at the app, it's okay if there's no problem.
If you're uncomfortable with that much, it's better not to force yourself to eat, but I
used to eat a lot of 600g at first, and
there was even a time when I ate 500g three times a day. Especially in the beginning,
I ate like that. If I ate a lot, I went to the teacher and said, "I want to gain weight,
what should I do?" So, I told him to eat a lot of calories and eat three times a day,
so I
ate 500g of meat and a lot of baby meat. I
ate like that for almost a month and gained 1kg.
So, what is this? Looking at this, I can't eat a lot, so I
stopped after that, but
now I don't know what happened.  Eating just more fat and
more protein
doesn't seem to help much. When it comes to gaining weight, eating more fat and
graduating to more and more, you
can eat more. Fat accumulates more than you eat, so it's better to eat more.
Yes, anyway, that's a different story. If you
can eat meat at 4 in the morning, you can eat more than 200g in the morning. It might be
better if you can divide the rest between your shoulders. If you're
thinking of fasting, eating only one meal a day is a good idea. The amount may be a little more,
but if you come
in after eating, it can be done. It
depends on the absorption rate and other factors, but in fact, there are
2 animals that originally had a cumulative fast.
Most animals eat a lot at once and then sleep for a few weeks before coming out to
hunt.
People also do that a lot late in the day. If you look at traditional tribes, most of them
fast. He said that he fasts a lot, and that means he fasts a lot, but it's not like he's eating a lot of food at once.  They
eat a lot.
There's a tribe of Eskimos called
Chuck Chil. Chuck Chibu is famous for its food fighters. It's mentioned in Dr. Pal's book. They have
four kinds of crabs. These days,
there are people who believe in food just because they film mukbangs.
I'm not trying to belittle them at all, but let me give you an example. Like, "
Oh,
how's the fragrance?" "Yum,"
who else?
There was this person on the winning channel who was a really good eater. Anyway,
there are people who eat really well these days, but they
don't have any experience. There were a lot of years of accumulation among those who didn't have any experience.
Among the people Dr. Pyce created in Touch, the best eater
ate one meal a day in the evening. He would
sit down and eat a two-year-old male reindeer, or a slow-cow,
in one sitting. He would sit there and eat a lot, and he would eat incredibly fast. It was
a bit competitive, like a contest, and
there was a bit of a competition among them. The person who was rumored to be the best eater would sit down and eat a
registered two-year-old male reindeer in one sitting. He would eat it all. He would even eat a
deca.  They say that there were people who swelled up like this and
fell asleep and the next day, they would
wake up and do other things while holding on to objects, and the next day, they couldn't move at all. They said that even
if you live like this, you can live healthily, so you
should be a monster and develop well.
Yes, yes, in that sense, eating 600g each time is
not a big deal if it's not too difficult for you.
If you're worried, you can add the three supplements above. You
may need to rest your fat a little longer. Is 50g a bit too much?
At work, too. As
I've mentioned several times before, the central nervous system
has the highest turnover rate in the body, so the nerves are regenerated and
new hair cells are created, and this is very slow, so it
takes a long time. It can take 5 years, but of course, it
can be helpful. It
provides all the necessary nutrients and removes all the unnecessary ones.  Let's go.
It's the basis of all treatments.
Especially, degenerative diseases and
neurological diseases, it
seems like it's extremely rare to grow taller by 4. If you're
worried about it coming up, it's not. The meat didn't spoil as much as I thought, and
even if it did, the
saw pin was 5,000 won. Thank you. I
picked it up yesterday. Oh, thank you.
Oh, it's disconnected. It went up more than I thought. The chat
was still a bit low, but should I
go down a bit? Hurry up and do it.
02. It doesn't spoil as much as you think, so you don't have to do more.
Even if it does,
humans are among the strongest animals.
Think about the 60 animals that come to mind right now.
Our stomach acid is 100 times stronger than theirs. Most of them are 100 times stronger than lions or penguins, so
you don't have to worry. Nothing. I'll call you. Now, just because the
wound heals, you might not suddenly want to eat the food you fought with,
but anyway, the meat doesn't spoil easily, and even if you always do it,
I don't have a problem. If it's going to
come up already, it's better to change to a single agent. In fact, Aronamin Gold.  I'm going to
talk about vitamins that are better than I thought, like Gold. There are fewer people, but the
content has increased, and more isn't necessarily better. I mentioned that there's nothing like this, and you have to
eat a lot of it in a form that's neither activated nor popped. Rather, it's better to eat a lot of vitamin B6, which is more kinetic and has more vitamin
B3. I don't recommend it anymore, and it's expensive. There's a perception that vitamins like B3 and B6 are
okay because they're excreted anyway,
but that's not true. Fat-soluble vitamins accumulate in the body and are dangerous, so you have to eat a lot of refined vitamins. You have to be careful with delayed-release vitamins. But that's not true. Fat-soluble vitamins are dangerous because they accumulate in the body, so you have to eat a lot of them.
However, in reality, fat-soluble vitamins are 4, which we can eat in megadoses at any time in a natural state. For example, in the case of Kita May, if
we catch an animal, take out its liver, and eat a lot, we
can eat a megadosage at any time.
Vitamin D is dangerous because we
can receive 100,000 won worth of UC a day if we take it in the sun or take it with our clothes off.
We always take that fat-soluble vitamin D.  You can eat it, but
in nature, you can never take the crazy amount of water-soluble vitamins that are in a single pill.
The same goes for vitamin C. The B complex, too, is what Big was trying to talk about, but
sustained-release vitamins like Megalos are often extremely safe.
Assuming you take a balanced diet with other vitamins,
there are many cases where vitamins on the web are not very safe, contrary to the perception that they are safe. In the long term, Watson, especially,
is like a knife, but Aronamin Gold is always B1, which is prosthetic thiamine,
so
it's well absorbed. The rest of the B vitamins don't have a lot of body weight,
so there's not much risk.
Um, that's why my mouth is gradually getting
darker. My lips and
face are eating them one by one.
Plus, they're not being restored.
So, I don't think it's bad for Aram to see
it. It's also good to make sausages. Carrying around Salam and stuff is different. Originally, the storage theory was different. Mina
or
America first exempted it. What is it?
It's a mixture of fat, jerky, lava, and teller.
Pelican Pelican If you make something like that and carry it around, that's the first traditional habitat, right?
Hello, David Jeon. It
seems like it
would be better if you eat it in liquid form. It's
better if you drink that much, but you won't gain weight. Yes, if you eat that food together, you'll add a lot of mountain goat rice, so of course you'll swell up.
If you adjust the food a little bit, then
Asiba pivot is right? I thought of Habibi and no, it's a fight about the settlement amount, but
the issue was fierce. It seems like it was similar to the agreement, but I thought about it a little bit and it
wasn't planned, but it's a wheel. It's
Ebaviba Baby, so I thought about one agreement. The remaining 9 did
n't work out. I don't think there's anything I can do other than not drinking alcohol and getting enough sleep.
And sometimes I do it and say I'll eat steel battalion, so I
did it with brute force. Asada Jiro does it. To detoxify the liver and improve its needs,
rest is the best. Are there any foods that are good for the liver?
The liver is good because it contains all the nutrients the liver needs, starting with
peptides.
It's good to always supplement and do it, so first of all, eat plenty of air protein and
ask a company that can supplement the sky. 4 requests
will help.
Egg whites can also help, but it's great. It's just a little vague, so yes,
but as you said, the most important thing is to reduce alcohol or other things that the liver
needs to recover. So,
adding glutathione would be even better. Also, it can help next time, but
writing about glutathione urban is the best. The
pastors started by not eating a lot of food and
reducing oil. It's okay. Stress itself creates a dinner environment.
4 arrived. The
feet are not cold. Paul shop. Actor. A few days, there won't be a g100 kilo. Does that make sense? If you
finish with meat, it's 100 kilos. I don't know if it's because of that. Yesterday, through a two-
year-old s, Soca slow bangs were just asked. I
can't imagine that the French doctor referred to it as a bit of
MS.
So, the sound of water or 5 sheets of gas is high and the sound is loud. Why is that to me?
Those 2 3 supplements  You said you were eating it. I
think it would be good to check if
this is coming out well. If the abnormalities don't come out together, it could be because digestion is not going
well in the stomach and the stomach is not comfortable, and if it goes to the intestines, it's
4. If you
try using a variety of thumbnails, Ah, Chess, that video, sub, really, acne, whiteheads,
intermittent fasting, handbell, t-shirt, director's
site, Khan, looking at it, it's
unfamiliar. Khan's original is unfamiliar. In our country,
I don't have the talent to make island veils or things like that, so I sit down and watch my videos. It was
really hard to study blogs like this.
Yes, yes, this is
a bit of a problem. If I do it well, it would be really good.
Yes, it's not easy. If you make a video and add
a little exaggeration to the summer Patek and
think about it, like
this, I think the quality of the information itself is
very high. Why is it that the process of delivering and understanding it is
not smooth at all and it's very difficult to access and see?
Now, I'm making a crude video. And as I've been filming this year,
the number of prisoners has increased, and it's a bit surprising.
Ato lotion.
Then again, until I feel it again, it takes about 3 months. What is the right-side transplant cleansing method?
What is the 5th? I'm curious about that West Germany. I also need to take care of my skin, but I
don't remember where I went this time. Anyway, I need to make a passport. You can
see the request above for livelihood.
Crater Crater residing in the US,
please submit your tax information to AdSense so that we can accurately calculate applicable taxes on your income.
They said that all YouTubers should submit their tax information. I gathered this and I
need a passport to submit it. So my passport expired in August of last year, so
I'll do that.
Oh, what's this? I came here to take pictures. I do
n't really like photo assets. Sigma, but what is it? Now that I have to take pictures face-to-face,
taking pictures isn't really bad. If you
take evidence photos, little by little, like this, it
doesn't look much better than a long one. If you
look at it here, it really does make your skin better. And then, the asymmetry of the face and jaw is
made symmetrical. It's
a bit big. But it looks much better than now.
So, first of all,  Even if it's skin, facial asymmetry seems difficult to do, and how can I
chew meat symmetrically? I have to
find swelling and have it every day, but I don't want to think about that much,
but I feel like it would be good if I put in some effort,
but the number of viewers is higher than usual.
Now, I already do a lot of toys 4. I
do it.
r on
m clothes.
In the past, I wrote it down according to the description 3, but these days, I
don't remember if I omitted it.
At the time, what was it? Yes, the phone is actually good for the entire body.
Please subscribe, like, and set notifications. It's good to let other people know a lot.
Yes, forget it.
Later, if you do that, you can do it
together.
This and that. When doing the same thing in chaos,
as a sharer, what is it? Page 15
1. That's
it. First, find a small amount. I think I should be a special envoy. It's
only the eyebrows, but Jesus wore a mask. It's the right side. It's the ground. It's
not worse than a burn. The skin is better.
Then, more. Now, I'll eat whatever I want. Now, it's a new world.
Oh, I've
suddenly
heard a lot about the redeemer these days. It's a little short.
There was no such thing as maturity, but I heard it quickly.
Yes, that's why I don't eat olive oil, coconut oil, or
avocado oil. I think I heard a lot of reader stories, but this is different from other forms of mine. 3 Most of them are around 500 in this group. 4 Lee Man-hee of the usage survey passed. Suddenly, it went down a bit. 4 Hazel. So,
in the 3c comments, there were a
lot of comments saying that I was tired,
so it was a bit like that.
Ah, like this, yes, instead, I followed the instructions to wipe the wet skin.
Yes, I did that, but because of the awkwardness, I think it burned a lot.
After squeezing it right away, it was 287. The
total number has definitely increased, and even if people pass by here and there, people who
normally watch my videos are only watching the amount, but now
that I've come out like this, I think there are a lot of comments here and there.
Since I don't burn any members, my books will gradually do as they are.
Ah, ah, ah, clothes. If I just keep doing it consistently, it might
be okay even if it freezes. I just think so. Even now, I
'm uploading videos every day, so it's not that much.
Yes, no. These days, I'm telling myself to run
a little even if I let go, so I can overcome it.
Double mini.  Thank you for 30,000 won more.
Do you know about this? I am grateful. If so, I
will write a thank you post to reporter Yang Jeong-ah.
Ah, tomorrow,
I will continue to Nop.
Ah, Vivian, you must be going to Norpok. High. Sometimes, the yolk is in the hand.
I haven't done it in a long time,
but these days, I will be at home. Dad puts more eggs in, so I just use it. But this is a foundation here. It means peeling eggs cheaply, and it is difficult to buy things like Oasis like before. I could
only buy one of the original plates that were chosen on the same day. So, I do
n't have anything to eat, and it is quite dry. These days, I just don't use the yolk and
only use water. It's okay. I
am 25 years old. I do farming, and I am straightforward, but it is
not easy. So now, I am poisonous and I am on
YouTube. Noun and verb eyesight 5.
Below, like this photo.
Yes, I
am trying to do something, but there are many difficulties.
Ah, Dr. Jang is not doing well. So, I
want to return to farming in the video.  Ah, I feel like there's going to be a sudden change of pace again from Pyeongchang to Taebaek. I do
n't really know what Jesus is. What's going on? Oh my,
why are these products like this? It's not that applying them indiscriminately is bad, but if you just don't do
them and live, you know, shampoo and things like that, when I used to go somewhere, I'd pack 3 frangipani and lotion and stuff, but I
go to the airport and stuff like that. If I go somewhere, I'll pack a lot of them. But these days, even if it's not that bad, I remember going back and forth like this to the US.
When I go there, I'll pack
sesame ramen. My mom used to say that ramen was like that when she went to the US. And she'd give me sesame ramen
and music. Did the sesame ramen cups actually
hold that much volume? So, Young-gil would put them in a separate G-cup and stack the cups on top of each other and do weird things like that and carry them around. Of course, they
were delicious. But
now, when I go somewhere, I don't pack lotion or shampoo.
1 frangipani. Body Earth Earth Map  Well, my Seonyeong
doesn't wear anything and eats food from customers, but meat is sold everywhere you go.
You buy it and
eat it. If you really feel like it's not enough, you can't cook at the barn at home and say that you can just go to the mart and eat it. If you think about it that way, it's really simple. There's nothing you can't eat wherever you go. If you take medicine and something else,
if you feel like it's a problem, you can fast.
For example, I thought I was going to die from fasting, but now it's not like I'm going to do it again for a few days.
4.
Shampoo bar, Chasi foam, cleansing lotion, cosmetics.
But these are things that women don't use. It seems like you'll need a little more furniture. There must be a
lot more than just the men who don't use it, but
Vice President Sam
will sell HCL supplements, herbs, and nosebleeds. Among them, if you only buy ones that don't contain ingredients, please come to
Kao Share Neka. I think it would be good if you can grow. You have to prepare whether you got Kao 3
or got it somewhere.
Ah, it's
really fast and
there's a k in it.
Ah, you can take it before eating, during eating,
after eating, or all three times. I mean, it's
usually more effective to take it before, but it's
okay to take it in between. If
I explain this simply, I'll
just explain the concept of the sun, so please
take the eye color test. Ka, yeah,
it's like this.
How do I boil the picture? The PPT version changed when the computer changed,
so it was a bit different. It came out in various ways.
So how do I give it to you?
This doesn't seem to be a square, but it's something like
this.
What do I do?
It's lf point 2010. Does
anyone know how to draw a 2010 400 million picture? Like this.
4 I'll have to look it up later.
If you can't draw, you can go to the middle canvas and
draw a picture.
Today, they especially did it.
Oh, right, sex is not it. I'm the
digital native. Young people, that is, aimag ike ket,
not that old, but I don't know much about it.
These things are
not as good as you think on the internet, but computers.
So how can I draw well
? I'll explain it to you in words. Why did I make it like that? It was just
wasting time.
We're in a circle like this. It's
really simple, but I wish I could draw it like a dark dive.
But hey, it opens up like this and
it's okay. If
there's a child, food comes down from the top to the esophagus like this. It comes
down through the pylorus and is closed like this. The
nanny usually doesn't stop going down. 1 Even in the rain,
when it all comes down later, the pylorus should be here together. It doesn't go up inside the station, so
block it on both sides.
And to go down from here, it has to be fully digested for the black people.
Here, 1 is strong in favor, so neutralize Samsung. Here,
freeze the diary and
when the neutralization is to a certain extent, write like this from the bottom.
When the neutralization is complete, Annie opens again and comes down again.
When the food is blocked like this, it piles up.
Chew it thoroughly and swallow it. But  The speed at which food accumulates is generally
faster than the speed at which it comes out of the stomach.
This is why you should eat slowly to improve digestion and not speak too hastily. The
stomach has limited space, so if you
eat too quickly before the small intestines are fully empty and peristalsis occurs, food
will accumulate to the level of gastritis. Then, digestive juices will be released, and food will accumulate like this. In addition to the digestive juices that accumulate in the second stomach,
food will also accumulate. Then,
from there, it has to be dissolved and introduced from the outside in.
This is a time-consuming and difficult process. If all of this is not possible, the lower part of the stomach will
open and undigested food may pass into the stomach.
Therefore, eating the entire food is helpful. Walking outside for a short while is also
helpful. When
our bodies exercise too vigorously, blood flow must be sent to that area. When digestion occurs,
blood flow to the digestive system is completely blocked. This is where we
need to focus more this year.
Walking is good for digestion.  It's not that bad, but shaking your arms and legs
doesn't require that much blood flow, so you don't really have to worry about it, but that step
creates a shock and a shock, and the movement replaces some kind of physical
coordinated movement. I've
completely lost track of the story, and this isn't easy, so the body takes over and
moves the legs, and it's like going back and forth
by inertia. Just moving the body like this will help, but
rather than continuing like this, isn't it more natural to just walk? I'm
asking you to take even two steps for a walk.
This hypocrisy isn't just coated on the outside, but a little more compact. So, the
surface area can meet and mix together
- 2. You can think of it as something like that.
Ah, there's a picture. Why didn't I think of a drawing board? I
use imps a lot, but I usually do.
Ah, the whiteboard looks like it's upside down, but it's actually the whiteboard.
It's on the side with the wooden board, and on the other side, we have 1-ri and things like that. It's packed.
Last time I came, the
3rd season wasn't approved for distribution. It was
n't even a call, so if you distribute it now,  No, my brain is
messed up. It's like I'm not using the Wi-Fi right now,
and I'm using Spotlight. That's why the red 9-
pack icon appears and then it's like that.
In the summer, you should get a lot of taffeta. It's also good to get a lot of sunlight on your skin, so
of course, it's not good to get too tanned, but it's good to expose your skin to light for an appropriate amount of time.
But in the comments on the tube, there are
a lot of comments that are a bit embarrassing.
Animals are our friends.
People with that kind of ability come and write a lot of comments like that. And some
radicals also write comments.
Ah, but now, because that keeps happening, I answered a few questions at first,
but I know, I'm tired. But when I brush past those people,
YouTube itself doesn't respond to comments. So, actually, I
don't reply to YouTube comments these days.
Okay, then that won't work either.
4 Um, okay. It's just like that.
Car. It seems tiring to play deck on YouTube. My
stepmother's place is a cafe. At least sometimes, if you eat it, you can.
There are some who say, "Does it make sense to say it's not good?" But still, there are
more people who agree with the overall framework, so
there are still many people who know that there is such a thing as a second-level insult. So, I
thought I could just do that kind of commenting, but these days, of course, in cafes,
there are extreme big ones like our Cafe Sica and 5,
so eating meat is a good thing, and since I'm out at a time like this, there's
nothing like that, but it's a bit easier to go to a helmet and
leave comments on YouTube.
So, I don't leave comments much these days. But, you know,
I do a lot of things on YouTube, including blogs. These days, you
can say that I'm a blogger. But
most of them are cafes and YouTube high-tech, and then KakaoTalk chats, and
so on. KakaoTalk chat rooms,
YouTube, Naver Cafe, etc.
But now, there are definitely people who are only active on each platform. Some
people who started at cafes and later moved to chat rooms, and some
who only look at cafes. They create a system, and even if they are qualified,
then
after that  There may be people who only watch YouTube, but YouTube
has a lot more color, so
even though I have over 100 subscribers, it's
not like they're all watching. But there will be a lot of people who watch it if you look below.
Those people have nothing to communicate with. In fact, I do the live broadcast once a week, and
even that's during prime time on the weekend. During that time,
there will be a lot of people who are not listening to the broadcast. It's during that
time when a lot of other things are happening. It seems like this app is during prime time, so I'm
doing it a little bit, but anyway,
those people have to communicate through comments on the body tube. I'm
not replying to their comments because of the people in Jang-an, so it's a bit of a problem.
Okay, anyway, it
might take longer than you think to buy milk from our farm. It might take longer than you think, or it might take shorter than you think. I do
n't know about that either. When will it be?
Regarding cosmetics, what do you
think about sunscreen? Did season 2 come out? The
story is clear.
Um,
sunscreen is not recommended.
Physically blocking sunlight
can help. And then some natural products.  There are things like loving nature,
like applying sunscreen thickly, Coco, etc., which are good, but just because you
don't skip out on sunscreen doesn't mean you should never use it. If
we don't use natural sunscreen, there are situations where we have no choice but to be exposed to the sun. I think it's not good to apply
sunscreen indiscriminately or apply it whenever you go out.
But even if you do something like this this time,
or go somewhere and work at night, or use
brown cotton, especially in the summer, you can't avoid exposure for a long time. If you
go out fully armed, it's not like that, but it's not that bad. In
those cases, applying it can be more helpful.
It's true that getting too much UV rays is definitely bad for your skin. But now, in general,
when the sunlight is strong, do you go out on purpose? In fact, get more vitamin
D. It's synthetic. Even if you use melamine or an
online specialty, it's more. Now, I
suddenly saw a happy division for life on OnePorter, or I applied sunscreen too diligently my whole life,
and the sunlight is now reducing the melanin pigment.
In a situation where you're not feeling well and not prepared at all for UV rays, one day you suddenly
forget to apply sunscreen,
or maybe the
ocean is out for 3 hours and your sunscreen runs out,
and if you suddenly expose your body to a lot of UV rays, the
chances of developing skin cancer greatly increase.
Yes, because of that, there are other people who apply sunscreen at home and look good,
but I don't think that's very good.
Since the development of sunscreen, the incidence of skin cancer has skyrocketed.
There are many things that are bad for marine life because of applying sunscreen and interpreting it. As
I just mentioned, there are ways to use sunscreen to improve skin health. I think there are ways to do
that, but when I just said it as a counterargument, I do
n't think it's very good.
Or there are products that only block UV rays.
New cars are ridiculous. UED synthesizes vitamin D, and it
creates wrinkles and damages DNA in the skin. UBA UV rays are the ones that go around. Let's
look at the probability of life.
Where did it go?
Please try it once.
Oh, later.  Let's take a look at what I don't forget. There
are too many skins below,
so it's better to eat cake or something cleaner. It doesn't matter if you eat carbon dioxide. It's
not like you can eat the semester or anything like that at any time.
Why can't you do something rather than doing nothing? You
should think about that. Ah,
just blocking someone. I've
loved someone who was really ridiculous in the past, but I don't block
them and say
how much exemption they have. I wonder if it will be helpful for those who see the comments later. It was the first time,
but those people left the first part and left comments and started a discussion there. It
couldn't be like that. I
just made a reservation. When comments like this came up one by one every five days, it
became a joke. I do
n't know these days, but I wonder if it's right now. But it
's also a bit strange to just clean up all that stuff.
What's better than raw meat? For example,
there are some things that are better than chicken, but
why does chicken have a budget so high?
It's a bit difficult to raise a healthy baby by only eating chicken. The risk is still too high, reaching close to 20%.
In that sense, it's better to look at foods that are low in linoleic acid. It's
hard to eat 2kg for 5,000 won, but if you can buy the cheapest ones from meat boxes,
there are some that are cheaper than you think. There are some that are less than half a kilo,
so I think eating those would be really good. I'm
growing vegetables in Australia, and now I'm enjoying a church.
But there are people like that now. We don't kill rats to eat them, so it
doesn't matter. I do
n't know how that happens. Why is
n't the nutritional value of treatment calendar?
It's much lower than that of eggs. Eggs. The larger the egg, the more nutrients it contains.
Just when I was talking about the counterargument,
there's much more of it in duck eggs than in
chicken eggs.
Of course, there are also three types that eat a lot of feathers.
In a short period of time, the increase in growth hormone secretion and IGF-1 due to the suggestion of arithmetic suggests that it's actually better.
There's an opinion that it leads to an increase in the incidence of cancer. What do you think?
As in the column, I recorded a video. I'd like you to watch it. It's said that when a
mare stops praying, she wears a mask and eats three meals a day, and
when she's on a low-carb diet, the ice circle increases, and that IGF-1
increases the incidence of cancer. Oh, there's an app called the Bible.
4. Red products increase IGF and freezing. It
's a micro caster. So, you have to drink a lot of ginseng water to get
it to happen.
And,
unless we give her additional
support for growth, it prevents the body from breaking down. It's a hormone that protects the bone density from decreasing. It
's not a hormone that makes the body grow. Even if you
just breathe quietly, you can build muscle and make it like that. It's not a circle. It
seems like the internet is not good.
4. You don't have to worry about this.
As you reproduce, you meet the demand due to iron deficiency. It's
not that big of a deal. I don't think I've achieved much.
In fact, there's talk about that in the vegan community. Oh, and there's also a
lot of that in the comments on my video.  There are people who know,
if you're going to ask if I eat human meat, then
yes, but this is
something that's unsustainable within the community, so we have
no choice but to eat human corpses.
So, what do
people say? Now, in order to protect animals, human life has become less important. If
I were to receive slurry in a situation where I don't have to receive it,
if I hadn't been vegan and eaten meat, I would
n't have been anemic and wouldn't have received it again, right? By
receiving it like that, there are
people who absolutely need to receive it in situations where there's a traffic accident or something, and there's a chance that they won't be able to receive it. And there's a chance that someone
might hurt someone else while trying to protect the passage.
4 It
seems like those aspects aren't well considered, so I
keep eating a lot in the National Assembly, and Jeong Myeong is okay, but I don't eat it, so I always
get good evidence.
First, I think it would be better to adapt to the ketosis state a little more. You
should also get tested to see if you have a thyroid. The most important thing is to
reduce linoleic acid.
Naver is continuing now.  Those are the ones that
seem to be buffering. It seems like it's going to disconnect. Go and write now. It's
getting
late and it's time to stop now. It's really late. It's time to sleep now, so I'll
finish it up quickly. Next time, I'll do it again next week. The
next time is Saturday so that I
can get used to it. Yes, that person, don't eat meat. Why are you eating that poor thing? I heard that it was sweeter than I thought, but this is a bit much. There are many people who write it. If you write it big, it's a record. I can see it,
but if you press the place and look, it's
gone. There were a lot of those.
Anyway, I think it would be good to eat more in one meal, and it's
good to use more land. As BB said, reducing linoleic acid
seems to be the most critical. That seems to be the most important.
Thank you for watching the set. I'll do it again next week.
Oh, me. Once in a while, these people.